It’s not only what you say, it’s how you say it.
We will explore the art of delivery and give you tips and techniques that you can use in a variety of settings.
It is so critical to make sure that you’ve done the hard work around structuring your message, around creating a clear and compelling storyline.
It would be a shame to have it all fall down at the moment of delivery.
There are a lot of different ways that you can inject energy into your delivery, but also ensure that you’re going to keep your audience engaged,
and they will walk away knowing the most important things.
And that’s why we want to explore the different elements of vocal delivery, your physical presence, and things that you can use in a variety of settings to ensure that the way you tell your story,
the way you deliver your message, is just as impactful as the content of that message. One of the videos I love watching is the Will Stephen TEDx address,
where he actually talks about absolutely nothing as he’s delivering a TEDx talk,
but his vocal delivery, his physical presence, is so engaging, he creates a real emotional connection with the audience. And meanwhile, he’s talking absolute gibberish.
But what it does do is it drives home the idea of how you can divorce the content of your speech or your presentation
and really see how the vocal, physical techniques can come to life.
There are a lot of techniques of what you can do with your voice, whether that’s intonation, emphasis, speaking more softly, drawing your audience in.
We will explore that with one of our experts a little later.
And in terms of physical presence, again, you may have seen things about the power pose or what have you,
but there are ways that in your physical presence, whether you’re in a small group setting or a large group setting, you can use and deploy physical presence in a different way.
And in terms of creating an emotional connection with your audience, this is really going into the element of conversation.
So imagining that, whether you’re just with one person or a room full of people, how do you create a sense of emotional connection with them?